(Leonard:)What are you doing?
Every Saturday since we've lived in
this apartment I have awakened at 6:15...
...poured a bowl of cereal,
added a quarter cup of milk...
...sat on this end of this couch, turned on
BBC America, and watched Doctor Who.
(Leonard:)Penny's still sleeping.
Every Saturday
since we've lived in this apartment...
...I have awakened at 6:15,
poured myself...
(Penny:)I know.
Look, you have a TV in your room.
Why don't you have breakfast in bed?
(Sheldon:)Because I am neither an invalid
nor a woman celebrating Mother's Day.
(Penny:)What time is it?
Almost 6:30.
(Penny:)I slept all day?
No, it's 6:30 in the morning.
(Penny:)What the hell is your problem?
(Sheldon:)Okay, this cereal
has lost all its molecular integrity.
(Sheldon:)I now have a bowl
of shredded wheat paste.